Hello and Welcome to 'What is Your Emergeny'!
Next
To play, simply click on the phone and respond to the caller's emergency by clicking on the computer.
Next
Recruiter: Hello I’m here to help you learn what it’s like to be a 9-11 operator. I have set it up so that you will be given a certain amount of calls to help you learn how to handle different situations that you will experience in the workplace. I’ll be giving you tips as you progress.
Next
Recruiter: Start by telling them who it is and asking what their emergency.
Next